question: "In 1768, Captain James Cook set out to explore which ocean?",
a: "Pacific Ocean",

b: "Atlantic Ocean",

c: "Indian Ocean",

d: "Arctic Ocean",

correct: "a",



question: "What is actually electricity?",
a: "A flow of water",

b: "A flow of air",

c: "A flow of electrons",

d: "A flow of atoms",

correct: "c",



question: "Which of the following is not an international organisation?",
a: "FIFA",

b: "NATO",

c: "ASEAN",

d: "FBI",

correct: "d",



question: "Which of the following disorders is the fear of being alone?",
a: "Agoraphobia",

b: "Aerophobia",

c: "Acrophobia",

d: "Arachnophobia",

correct: "a"



question: "What is the speed of sound?",
a: "120 km/h",

b: "1,200 km/h",

c: "400 km/h",

d. "700 km/h",

correct: "b",



question: "Which is the easiest way to tell the age of many trees?",
a: "To measure the width of the tree",

b: "To count the rings on the trunk",

c: "To count the number of leaves",

d: "To measure the height of the tree",

correct: "b",



question: "What do we call a newly hatched butterfly?",
a: "A moth",

b: "A butter",

c: "A caterpillar",

d: "A chrysalis",

correct: "c",



question: "In total, how many novels were written by the Bronte sisters?",
a: "4",

b: "5",

c: "6",

d: "7",

correct: "d",



question: "What was the first country to use tanks in combat during World War I?",
a: "France",

b: "Japan",

c: "Britain",

d: "Germany",

correct: "c",



question: "Which two months are named after Emperors of the Roman Empire?",
a: "January and February",
b: "March and April",

c: "May and June",

d: "July and August",

correct: "d",